There's obviously a mistake.
明顯是弄錯了
We were notified the passes would be waiting in our names.
有人通知我們各自的票已經準備好了
I'm sorry, but that's incorrect.
抱歉  但不是那樣的
- Morf Vandewalt, Artweb. - No. It's today...
-莫弗·范德瓦爾特  藝術網站  -不  是今天
Hey, Morf.
你好  莫弗
Okay, I wanna speak to someone in charge, please.
我要和這里的負責人談談
- Lovely to see you again. - This is ridiculous.
-很高興再次見到你  -簡直荒謬
We bought Shogrun's Ultraworld last month in New York.
我們上個月在紐約買了舒格倫的「超世界」
Have you ever felt invisible?
你感受過被忽視嗎
Once, I built a railroad.
我曾經建過鐵路
- There he is. Morf. - Cloudio.
-你在這啊  莫弗  -克勞迪歐
It's Kenji, you probably know. It's titled Hoboman.
你估計知道了  這是建治的作品  叫「流浪俠」
The response is amazing.
反響非同一般
Arguably, the hit of the show.
可以說  是整個藝術展的亮點
Wolfson, Female Figure, four years ago.
沃夫森的「女性雕塑」  四年前的老把戲
No, it's new. Vastly different themes.
不  這是全新的  截然不同的主題
It's an iteration.
新瓶裝舊酒罷了
No originality. No courage. My opinion.
毫無原創  沒有勇氣  我這樣認為
Well, I absolutely respect the power of your point of view,
我絕對尊重你個人觀點的權威
but this encompasses on a global scale.
但這個作品涵蓋全球
There's just such a sense of now and in your face,
當下感奪人眼球
which speaks to pop and cinema and economics.
表達了流行音樂  電影和經濟
I mean, you can feel the winds of the apocalypse.
你可以感受到一股末日之風
I can't save you.
我救不了你
We have a four-million-dollar hold, a major buyer in Shanghai.
有人愿意用400萬美元買下  是上海的大買家
Will you be running your review today?
你今天會發表評論嗎
Do you have a minute?
你有空嗎
No, I'm just heading inside now.
沒有  我要進去了
- I have to tell you something about Ricky. - What?
-我要告訴你一件有關瑞奇的事  -怎么了
- Josephina, he's cheating on you. - Are you serious?
-約瑟芬娜  他出軌了  -你認真的嗎
- I saw him with this girl. - When?
-我看見他和一個女孩在一起  -什么時候
Last night at a bar.
昨晚在一個酒吧
- What? - They were both pretty drunk.
-什么  -他們都喝得很醉
- Wha... What time? - I don't know. Ten?
-幾點鐘  -不清楚  大約十點
- They were all over each other. - Right at the fucking bar.
-他們打得火熱  -就在酒吧里
- I'm so sorry, Josephina. - Are you sure it was him?
-真遺憾  約瑟芬娜  -你確定是他嗎
They were standing right next to me.
他們就站在我旁邊
I gotta go.
我得掛了
- Anything I can do? - No.
-有什么我能做的嗎  -沒有
Uh, thank you, seriously. Bye.
謝了  真的  再見
- Howzit, Morf? - Hello, Jon.
-還好嗎  莫弗  -你好  喬恩
Really something, eh?
很了不起  是吧
Is Piers sleeping with Dorothy?
皮爾斯和桃樂西有一腿嗎
Oh, I'm certain you'd have to ask him that.
那你得問他本人了
Excuse me.
失陪
- Morf, love. - Oh, Gretchen.
-莫弗  親愛的  -格雷琴
We bid on it for the museum.
我們為博物館競標下了這幅畫
Jon wants three point seven.
喬恩想出370萬買下
Rhodora would never sell a Piers for under five,
洛多拉絕不會低于500萬賣皮爾斯的作品
so it's a nice opportunity for us.
所以這對我們來說是個好機會
I'm quite curious to know what you think.
我很好奇你是怎么想的
I think sober hasn't been good for him.
我覺得戒酒對他不利
Well, this was done fifteen years ago.
這是他在15年前完成的
Piers was in the full bloom of alcoholism here.
正是皮爾斯當時酗酒最嚴重的時候
Exactly.
沒錯
So, you're saying it is a good buy for the museum, then?
所以你覺得這對博物館來說挺劃算
Excuse me.
失陪
Josephina.
約瑟芬娜
Are you okay?
你還好嗎
Literally, the worst fucking day.
絕對是最糟糕的一天了
Ugh, your makeup.
你的妝都花了
God, I'm late.
天吶  我遲到了
They texted, like, twenty times.
他們給我發了得有20次信息了
I'm headed there, too.
我也要去那兒
God, fucking people.
那些人真操蛋
- Who? - Everyone.
-誰  -所有人
Is Piers switching galleries?
皮爾斯要換畫廊了嗎
I answer phones and get coffee.
我就負責接電話和買咖啡
I'd literally be, like, the last to know.
就算是  我也會是最后知道的
You're too late. Rhodora already got her coffee.
你來太晚了  洛多拉已經拿到咖啡了
Are you where you wanna be?
你在這個位置真的滿意嗎
I'm not taking shit from the installer.
我才不要聽安裝工扯這一套
What did you think?
你覺得怎么樣
I haven't felt that in years.
我好多年都沒這種感覺了
- Morf is here. - Oh, thank you. Excuse me.
-莫弗來了  -謝謝  失陪了
Well?
怎么樣
Color. Life.
色彩  生命力
I love it.
我很喜歡
I'm sick of white spaces.
我受夠了空白的空間
That is so strange.
太奇怪了
I've been drawn to a bolder booth presence in terms
就作品和顏料而言  最近我瘋狂沉迷于
of work and palette lately.
更大膽的選擇
This adherence to showing in sterile, monochrome cubes.
堅持使用空洞  單色的立方體來構圖
It's just laziness. I wanted to get some juxtaposition going.
那只是偷懶罷了  我想把幾種東西并列起來
I'm actually, I mean right now,
我其實正在寫
writing something exactly about this.
有關這方面的東西
This wasn't in the catalog.
這不在目錄里面
It's Minkins.
這是明金斯的作品
It's called Sphere.
叫做「球體」
It creates this unique sensation,
它能根據不同的人
depending on each person
及他們決定去探索的洞
and whatever hole they decide to explore.
創造出獨特的感受
Just like life.
就和生活一樣
It uses all sorts of sensors and gizmos.
它使用了各種傳感器和小裝置
It's about choice, desire, sex.
它是關于選擇  欲望  性
The whole enchilada.
一應俱全
- It's groundbreaking. - Hmm, it's yours to break.
-這是突破性的  -由你來讓它突破
Debuted ten minutes ago.
十分鐘前才首次亮相
I'm posting a review. How much is it?
我要發一個評論  這個作品多少錢
So much easier to talk about money than art.
談錢比談藝術容易多了
Funny.
有意思
Speaking of, is Piers leaving you for Jon Dondon?
說起來  皮爾斯要離開你投靠喬恩·敦頓
I've represented Piers for seventeen years.
我做皮爾斯代理人已經17年了
That's not an answer.
你沒回答我問題
Well, why don't you put your hand in?
你把手伸進去吧
See what you feel.
看看有什么感覺
- It's just not worth my investment. - You're mistaken.
-這不值得我去投資  -你錯了
This is gonna be an uncommon event experience,
這將會是前所未有的體驗
not to mention the tax incentive.
更不用說稅收激勵了
- Is there water in Miami? - At the bar, sir.
-邁阿密有水嗎  -在酒吧那邊  先生
- I don't know. - Fuck.
-我不清楚  -操
I can guarantee your position as co-chair--
可以確保你得到聯合主席的職位
Oh, excuse me. Piers.
失陪  皮爾斯
I was floating in the ocean, and, for this incredible moment,
在海洋中漂流著  而在絕妙的時刻
it felt like I had tapped into a primal consciousness.
我感受到自己的原始意識被激發了
A connection to the world in its purest form.
我與這個世界最存粹的形式相連
Ricky's still denying it.
瑞奇還不承認
"Please, baby, let me explain."
"求你了  寶貝  聽我解釋"
I swear to God, I want to hurt him.
我發誓  我想傷害他
Maybe it will free you up for new things.
也許這能讓你解脫去嘗試新鮮的東西
This was a new thing. He'd just moved in.
我們的關系就是新鮮東西  他才搬進來
I have to say,
我不得不說
I'm having my own major second thoughts about Ed.
我對跟艾德的關系有了遲疑
He actually has some fantasy about us getting married.
他居然對我們結婚抱有幻想
I'm through dating artists.
我不會再跟藝術家約會了
They're already in a relationship.
他們已經在跟藝術談戀愛了
Look, Damrish,
聽我說  達米什
your website doesn't give a sense of scale or texture.
你的網站并沒給人規模感和質感
But seeing your work in person at the new-artists fair,
但是親眼在新藝術家博覽會上看到你的作品
I had that "Oh, my God" moment.
讓我很是震驚
It charges and mauls and devours.
它會控制你  向你攻擊  吞噬你
Six months ago, I was living on the street,
六個月前  我流落街頭
showing on the sidewalk.
在人行道上展覽
So, that's where I'm coming from, right?
我的背景就是這樣的  對吧
Let me fill you in.
讓我跟你說清楚
All this...
所有這些
it's just a safari to hunt the next new thing and eat it.
只是獵殺下一個新事物然后吃掉它
I heard you were the one to watch out for.
我聽說要對你格外小心
I'm easy-peasy.
我是小菜一碟
Pussycat, really.
其實就是小貓
I know all about you, going back to your punk days.
我了解你的一切  之前那段朋克時光
Oof, that was many moons ago.
那可是很久之前的事了
- Velvet Buzzsaw. - Yeah, well, the name was catchy.
-天鵝絨圓鋸樂隊  -是的  名字很奪眼球
Yeah, the early stuff was great.
早期的作品很棒
Then it became, what? Like, self-parody?
然后呢  變成自嘲的黑歷史了
I mean, after Polly left,
波莉離開后
why'd you split up?
你們怎么就解散了
Who remembers through all the booze and pills.
那時候酗酒嗑藥那么多 誰還記得
But the point is,
但重點是
I've gone from anarchist to purveyor of good taste.
我從無政府主義者變成了有品位的供應商
So, I get the joke.
所以  我懂其中的把戲
None of this is new. It's all been done since
這都不新鮮  自從收取一塊骨頭來看壁畫
someone charged a bone to see the first cave painting.
就有人這么干了
Here you are.
給
So... Thank you.
所以  謝謝你
What cave are you showing in?
你在哪個畫廊展覽
Me and my dudes started a collective.
我和我的兄弟們搞了個系列
Well, cheers to that.
為它干杯
Well, hell knows, I love loyalty,
誰都知道我喜歡忠誠
but I would kill to exhibit you.
但我巴不得展出你的作品
I just turned down an offer for a full show from Jon Dondon.
我剛拒絕喬恩·敦頓給我辦個人作品展
And on and on.
真是沒完沒了
He's inside right now trying to poach Piers.
他正在里面想把皮爾斯挖過去
You know where I am, Damrish?
你知道我在哪嗎  達米什
I'm here doing shots with you.
我在這兒和你一起喝酒
Club soda. Lime.
蘇打汽水加青檸
The market always tiers up for you, Piers.
整個市場一直都對你翹首以盼  皮爾斯
Listen, my intolerance for your bullshit is zero.
聽我說  我已經受不了你這些屁話
Lekker, no bullshit.
好的  不說屁話
Look, Rhodora overpriced you.
洛多拉給你報價過高
She's lost it. She's completely out of touch.
她失去理智了  完全不了解最新的情況
I sold Cranial today for three point seven,
我今天以370萬的價格賣出了「顱骨」
exactly what I said I'd get.
和我預期的一樣
If you come with me, our gallery has cutting-edge analytics
如果你加入我  我們畫廊有最頂尖的分析技術
to maximize deal flow and global demand.
可以最大化交易流和全球需求
I am fighting to get back to creation, to revelation,
我正在努力重新創作  去啟發
the billion years of energy sparking through our brain.
我們大腦中閃爍了數十億年的能量
I'm not jetting around, hawking fucking tickets.
我才不會滿世界亂跑去賣展覽的門票
In an attention economy, celebrity is art form.
在注意力經濟中  名人就是藝術形式的一種
Do you understand that I only commission new work?
你知道我只委托新的作品嗎
Repros, prints, replicas are all marketed under my own brand.
復刻  印刷和仿制品都是以我自己的品牌銷售
My boet, I'm more than ecstatic
老兄  能與你在未來的作品上
to partner you exclusively on your future work.
進行合作  我非常高興
I hear Rhodora sold Sphere for seven million.
我聽說洛多拉把「球體」賣了700萬美元
Man, it's a carnival attraction.
老天  那作品不過是個嘉年華
It's brilliant.
那作品很棒
I never should've quit drinking.
我不該戒酒的
Josephina.
約瑟芬娜
Are you going to SLS?
你要去SLS嗎
I'm going to a satellite show outside of town.
我要去城外的一個小展覽
Well, I'll come.
我也去
What's going on with you?
你怎么了
What do you mean?
你什么意思
You're Morf fucking Vandewalt.
你他媽可是莫弗·范德瓦爾特
What are you doing coming to a grant show with me?
你和我去一個資助的展覽做什么
I like being with you.
我喜歡和你在一起
We have a taste relationship.
我們品味相投
Is that tobacco?
你抽的是煙嗎
Hash oil.
大麻油
Maybe I'll have one little puff.
要不我也來一小口
Okay, that was the worst show I've seen in years.
那是我這幾年來看過最差的展覽
And who was that angry guy when we left?
我們走的時候那個發火的人是誰
You don't know?
你不認識
That was Imeldus Vanderhorst. You panned him last year.
那是伊梅爾德斯·范德霍斯特  你去年抨擊過他
Grab two Tito's from the fridge.
從冰箱里拿兩瓶酒出來
You know, you're in much better shape than Ricky.
你的身材比瑞奇的好多了
I... do a lot of Pilates and Peloton.
我經常做普拉提和騎自行車
I remember your body.
我記得你的身體
I remember yours.
我也記得你的
Ever since Berlin, I find myself thinking all the time about you.
自打柏林之后  我一直都在想你
We were wasted.
我們當時都醉了
I keep telling myself that.
我也一直這樣告訴自己
Your skin.
你的皮膚
It's the most beautiful cross between almond and saddle brown.
是杏仁色和馬鞍棕之間最美麗的融合
I make you hard, huh?
我讓你硬了嗎
You make me confused.
你讓我困惑了
Tough headspace for a critic.
這對一個評論家來說太難了
Got back to LA late last night and looked at the numbers.
昨天很晚回到洛杉磯  看了下數據
My God.
我的天
Aside from the peachy Minkins sale,
除了明金斯的作品賣了個好價
Miami was really not a very great thriving market.
邁阿密不是一個非常繁榮的市場
Brass tacks, we didn't move one Rubek.
實際上  魯貝克的作品一件都沒賣出去
I know the London office has a hard-on for him,
我知道倫敦辦事處很想把他挖過去
but to my mind,
但在我看來
the last thing we need to waste time
他們最不應該把時間浪費在
on is trying to flog some pop-art revival.
出售復興的流行藝術品上
Pop-art.
流行藝術
Fuck me.
我操
"Star of the Nova section was
"明日新星區域獲獎作品是
Mertilla Splude's Go-Pro Kindergarten,
瑪蒂爾達·斯普拉德的Go-Pro幼兒園
an inspired disquisition of early-age experience."
對孩童時期經歷的卓越展現  頗受啟發"
Well, get inspired and come join me in the pool.
趕緊啟發自己和我一起跳進泳池吧
Is he all right?
他沒事吧
Call 911.
叫救護車
Who's supposed to be here?
誰該坐在這里的
Josephina. She's late... again.
約瑟芬娜  她...又遲到了
You, Rococo. Take the reception desk.
洛可可  你去前臺
It's... It's Coco, actually.
其實我叫可可
Haze Gallery. Can I help you?
迷霧畫廊  請問有什么需要
Hello?
喂
Hang up, right? Yeah, rich people are impatient.
已經掛了吧  對  有錢人就沒什么耐心
I'm really an artist, you know?
我其實也算是個藝術家
I did, um, Bandini's Froot Loop Hippo, you know that?
我畫了《班迪尼水果圈河馬》  知道嗎
And I glued on all the Froot Loops.
然后我貼在所有水果圈麥片上
Yeah.
嗯
It's at The Broad right now.
現在放在布羅德博物館呢
Not broad. People confuse it with Broad.
不是布洛德  人們總是搞混
- Broad, brode, yeah. - Right.
-布羅德  布洛德  -好吧
But I can get us tickets if you want.
但是如果你想去看  我可以搞到票
They know me there.
那邊的人認識我
- When did you get back? - Last night.
-你什么時候回來的  -昨晚
I have solid confirmation Piers has left you for Jon Dondon.
我有可靠消息稱皮爾斯離開你轉投喬恩·敦頓了
I'm going to get bored now.
我都快感到無聊了
This feels huge to me. Why would he leave?
我倒覺得這很嚴重  他為什么離開
Why, why why. Why anything?
為什么  為什么  什么為什么
Maybe I wanted him to leave.
也許我希望他離開
Meanwhile, I'm signing new talent.
同時我還簽了新的藝術家
Heard you got Damrish. He's fierce.
聽說你簽了達米什  他很厲害
And this morning, Mertilla Splude.
今天早上還簽了瑪蒂爾達·斯普拉德
We are on the same frequency, I swear.
我發誓  我們倆真是太搭了
Go-Pro Kindergarten's gonna break big.
Go-Pro幼兒園絕對會轟動
Your lips, God's ear.
你簡直就是上帝的枕邊人
Oh, wait. In our world, you are God.
等等  在我們的世界中  你就是神
And I'm running late. Gotta go.
我要遲到了  先掛了
Okay.
好的
I'm sorry.
對不起
Some random guy just, like, died in my building.
我們樓里突然死了個人
I really am so surprised.
我真是太驚訝了
Rhodora, I'm not kidding.
洛多拉  我沒和你開玩笑
A neighbor actually died. I found the body.
我的一個鄰居真的死了  是我發現尸體的
Bryson keeps me up to speed on everything
布萊森隨時向我匯報
that goes on around here.
這里發生的事
Your chronic lateness--
包括你經常遲到
Bryson's pissed because...
布萊森不爽是因為
he came on to me and I shut him down.
他追求過我  我拒絕了
He's a flat-out creeper.
他就是個混蛋
Well, I can say the interest I had in you has waned.
我只能說  曾經我對你抱有的興趣已經消磨光了
I thought I was grooming a protégé.
我原以為能好好培養你
All our long talks about your struggles and grand ambitions.
我們曾經就你的掙扎和遠大理想進行過無數次長談
And then you insult my intelligent mind.
而你卻侮辱了我的智商
I'm moving you off the front.
我要把你從前臺撤下來了
No client contact
不準再接觸客戶
until you raise the quality bar in your performance.
等你好好提升自己的藝術標準吧
- Morning. - Good morning.
-早上好  -早上好
Do we have Berlin? Singapore? London? Oh, we do.
柏林  新加坡  倫敦的都上線了嗎  看到了
So, I have two new favorite artists
我最近看上了兩名新的藝術家
I am all kinds of happy to tell you about.
我想向你們好好介紹一下
I'm from Perlack.
我是佩拉克公司的
We own the building.
這幢樓是我們的
Did you know him?
你認識他嗎
The guy who died?
死掉的那個人
Some sorta artist, I guess.
好像是什么藝術家
No.
不認識
I found his body.
是我找到他的尸體的
He liked his privacy.
他很注重自己的隱私
- He had a cat. - It's up there. We'll find it tomorrow.
-他有一只貓  -還在里面  我們明天找
Jesus, the stuff inside...
天啊  房間里的東西...
And it all gets tossed.
都要扔了
The old man wanted everything thrown away.
那老家伙本來希望把所有東西都扔了
No trace, his instructions.
他吩咐的  不留任何痕跡
Looks like he started to do it himself,
看來他都開始自己動手扔了
but he died before he could finish the job.
可惜還沒扔完  自己就死了
Well, good night.
晚安
Hey, kitty, kitty.
貓咪  貓咪
Hey, little guy.
小家伙
So glad you called.
你打來真是太好了
I'd hug, but I'm all sweaty.
我也想抱你  但我渾身是汗
Love the jumper. Cornsilk's a great color for you.
這件針織衫真不錯  玉米色很襯你
Miami was a revelation.
邁阿密堪稱天啟
Let me just start with that.
我就這么說吧
I don't know where I am with anything else in my life,
我不知道我的生命中還有其他
other than that I feel...
能比我和你一起時...
good with you.
感覺更好
So much better, and beyond good.
好多了  超乎尋常
I found something.
我發現了一點東西
That's what I'm saying.
我就是這個意思
Who did these?
這是誰畫的
What do you think of them?
你覺得這些畫怎么樣
They're visionary.
頗有遠見
Mesmeric. An absolute incredible...
令人癡迷  非常令人震驚的...
mix of mediums.
素材結合
I'm ensorcelled.
我完全傾倒了
- Do you think there's a market for it? - Massive.
-你覺得這些畫有市場嗎  -大市場
Beyond.
超大
Who represents them?
誰代理的
I do.
我
I'm dying with suspense.
我的好奇心快溢出來了
Who is it?
是誰
Tonight's jackpot is 400 million dollars.
今晚的大獎為四億
To win that jackpot, you must match these five white balls.
要贏得大獎  必須五個白球上的號碼全中
The first winning number tonight is 54. That's followed by 32.
第一個號碼是54   接下來是32
Up next we have 52. Your next number is 34.
接下來是52  下一個是34
Your final white ball for this Friday evening is 25.
本周五晚最后一個白球上的號碼是25
If no one matches the five numbers--
如果沒有人的號碼全中
It just seemed edgier at the Biennale.
雙年展時好像看起來很前衛一點
Oh, is this the exact lighting?
用的就是當初的燈光嗎
I think so.
應該是的
Okay, well, go check the specs.
你去核實一下規格
I run the collective Damrish belongs to.
我負責達米什那個系列的
I didn't think collectives had people in charge.
我不知道系列還有專門的負責人
Doesn't that defeat the whole purpose?
那不是就和系列的初衷不符了嗎
I represent him.
我代理他的
Used to.
曾經代理
We're building something away from all this commercial bullshit.
我們要創造跟這些商業垃圾完全不一樣的東西
It's not just about the fucking money.
這不僅僅為了什么錢
Stealing Damrish away would end us.
你奪走達米什會毀了我們
Okay. Well, you know what? He's not a child.
你知道嗎  他已經不是小孩子了
It's his choice, not mine.
這是他的選擇  不是我的
- You think this is done? - Back the fuck up!
-你覺得這就完了嗎  -給我后退
I tried to stop him.
我想阻止他的來著
Okay, well, you failed.
你失敗了
Unbelievable.
難以置信
- It will... never happen again. -Go!
-以后不會...再發生這種事了  -出去
Coco! Didn't you tell me you wanted to get a cat?
可可  你不是和我說過你想要一只貓嗎
Can we talk about it later?
我們能等會再聊嗎
Sure.
好的
What the fuck do you think you're doing?
你以為你在干什么
What is this? Who is this?
這是什么  這是誰畫的
That was under my desk.
這是放在我桌子下的
I was looking for tape and I saw this.
我在找膠帶  然后就看到了
- This is harassment. - Tell me who the artist is.
-你這是騷擾  -告訴我這個藝術家是誰
What the fuck is wrong with you?
你到底什么毛病
I do more than maintenance and packing.
我不僅僅只是個維修和打包的人
I'm not just a man of primitive skills.
我不是個單單四肢發達的家伙
This shit... talks to me.
這東西...和我有共鳴
Hey, you. I heard you were coming by.
你好啊  我聽說了你要來
I'm reviewing your Purlfoy exhibit.
我在評估你的珀爾福展覽
Be kind. Our membership is plummeting.
行行好  我們人手越來越少了
Tell me something.
告訴我
Have you ever heard of an artist named Vetril Dease?
你有沒有聽說過一個叫維特利爾·迪斯的藝術家
- D-e-a-s-e. - No.
-迪斯  -沒聽說過
Can you check?
你能查一下嗎
No. Not in our records, and we have everyone.
我們的記錄中沒有  我們可是記錄了所有人
Morf, honey, I, uh...
莫弗  親愛的  我
I need to bend your ear.
我要和你說一件事
I am leaving to become an art adviser.
我要離開這里  去當藝術顧問了
I know, I know. I can't say for whom.
我知道  我知道  我不能說是為誰
But I will be making enough
但是我賺的錢
to afford a terribly lovely car and garden.
足夠買一輛超棒的車和一個花園了
Oh, hello, Morf.
你好  莫弗
Hello, Jim.
你好  吉姆
Look, I came to the museum
我當初來藝術館
because I wanted to change the world through art.
就是為了想通過藝術改變世界
But the wealthy vacuum up everything, except crumbs.
但是財富吞噬了一切  只剩下一些碎屑
The best work is only enjoyed by a tiny few.
只有少數人才能欣賞優秀的作品
And they buy what they're told. So, why not join the party?
那些人聽人說該買什么就買什么  何不加入他們呢
It's everywhere, the money question.
什么事都離不開錢
In advance of my move, I am...
為了做好鋪墊  我正在
actively looking for purchases for my new client.
積極地為我的新客戶尋找藝術品
You might be interested to know
你說不定會感興趣
that I can provide to you a generous,
我可以給你提供一大筆
untraceable reward for anything
無法追跡的錢
you steer me to in the realm of
只要你給我提供一些
undervalued, pre-review, perhaps.
定價過低或是提前評估的作品
I don't do that.
我不做這種生意
What's your arrangement with Rhodora?
那你和洛多拉的協議呢
None.
沒有協議
Then her buys prior to your favorable reviews
那她總是在你給出好評價之前買下作品
are utterly prescient?
都只是有先見之明嗎
This is my life.
我的人生就是這樣
How I connect with some sort of spirituality at actual present.
我能和作品有一些精神上的聯系
Of course.
當然了
I assess out of adoration.
我的評價是出于我的欣賞
I further the realm I analyze.
我拓寬了我分析作品的領域
Forgive me, I...
原諒我  我...
Fuck.
操
Kisses.
親親
What's going on?
怎么了
You tell me.
你說呢
What are you doing here?
你來這里干什么
Hell's bells.
上帝啊
Bryson.
布萊森
- Incredible. - I'm going to have to ask you to leave.
-了不起  -我要請你離開了
Not if you had a gun.
除非你用槍指著我
It's none of your business.
這不關你的事
Oh, actually it is.
其實還真有關系
You signed a non-compete clause, which, if you read,
你簽署了競業限制條款  如果你好好讀了
you might remember is
你也許會記得
very much quite a lot broader than that.
你要做的可遠不止那些
Tell me all about Vetril Dease.
和我說說維特利爾·迪斯
His name is the tinsel on the tree.
他的名字簡直就是樹上的金箔
Don't make me pull some sort of heavy interrogation.
別讓我對你進行拷問了
Right now, it's just you and me,
現在  只有我和你
with all our active friendship and love for each other.
畢竟我們倆之間還有友誼和愛
Now, how did you get all of these?
你怎么得到這些畫的
A guy upstairs. He died.
樓上的一個人  他死了
And you just took them?
你就拿走了嗎
He had no family or friends.
他沒有家屬和朋友
Well, I won't bother with the obvious questions,
我就不問那些顯而易見的問題了
but, oh, you must have some giant plans.
不過  你肯定有一些大計劃吧
I invented do-it-yourself.
我是單干的行家
And you're in way over your head, babe.
你絕對搞不定的  寶貝
You have to archive and catalog and establish ownership.
你必須歸檔  分類并確認所有權
And monetize.
還要貨幣化
I'm willing to do all of that for... a reasonable percentage.
我愿意幫你做好這一切...只要合理分成
You can engage me in an endless lawsuit, or...
你可以跟我進行無盡的訴訟  或者
you can become rich and famous and successful.
你可以變得有錢  出名并成功
Which is what we both know you've always wanted.
我們都知道這是你一直以來夢寐以求的
We can claim the property was abandoned
我們可以說這些是被人遺棄的
if she says she found it in the dumpster.
前提是她說她是在垃圾桶里找到的
And took steps to find a rightful owner.
并著手尋找合適的主人
Well, first reports are he had no heirs.
初步報道聲稱他沒有繼承人
She's just a tenant. Could the building owner make a claim?
她只是個租客  大樓主人不能發個聲明嗎
The salvage guy said that they were junking everything.
那個處理的人說他們把所有東西都扔了
I mean, it took hours to carry it all down into my apartment.
我花了好幾個小時才把這些全搬到我的公寓
There was just so much of it.
實在是太多了
No, you found the art in the trash, not in his apartment.
不  你是在垃圾桶里找到畫的  不是他的公寓
This is very important.
這是很重要的
Now, remembering back, you found it in the dumpster.
回想一下  你是在垃圾桶里找到的
Isn't that what happened?
是那樣的嗎
The dumpster.
垃圾桶
Yeah, I remember now.
沒錯  我記起來了
Critique is so limiting and emotionally draining.
藝術評論太過局限又耗費心神
I've always wanted to do something long-form, beyond opinion.
我一直想要表達一種長期的  超脫的觀點
Dip my toe into an exploration of origin and essence.
將我的腳趾沉浸在對于原始和精華的探索中
A metamorphosis of spirit into reality.
靈體到現實的轉變
I've... I've never had the vehicle until now.
我一直沒找到表達的載體  現在終于有了
An artist toiling in the recesses,
一位藝術家在逆境中創作
discovered in death. I wanna start researching immediately.
被發現死亡  我想立刻開始研究
Well, there's timing. Meshing with our extensive marketing plans,
有個時間的問題  要和我們龐大的市場布局吻合
which we haven't gotten to yet.
我們還沒進展到那部分
Well, I'm willing to write the exhibit brochure.
我愿意寫展覽冊
That will give immediate weight to the launch.
能立刻推動展覽啟動
And in return, I want exclusive rights to a book
相應地  我想獨家擁有一本書
and several pieces.
和一些畫作
Well, that sounds swell.
聽上去不錯
Hi, Rhodora.
洛多拉
Well, I'm archiving his material,
我在歸檔他的材料
then running spectrums on his paint.
然后對畫作進行光譜解析
And it's the damnedest thing.
最奇怪的事情發生了
I don't even know how to account for it.
我都不知道怎么說明
I couldn't hazard a guess.
讓我不得不大膽猜測
Haze Gallery, please hold.
迷霧畫廊  請稍等
Yes, Josephina's unavailable right now, but I can take a message.
約瑟菲娜現在不方便接電話  但我能捎個信
Okay, please hold.
好  請稍等
Haze Gallery.
迷霧畫廊
Uh, yes. Rhodora is aware of the meeting,
對  洛多拉知道開會的事
but she's on a call right now.
但她正在打電話
You're positive it's the same Dease?
你確定是同一個人嗎
- Yeah. - Well, how can you be sure?
-對  -你怎么那么肯定
I visited the institution. I found his records.
我去了精神病院  找到了他的病歷
- Dear God. - I wouldn't worry.
-天啊  -換我不會擔心
The file's so old, there's no backup. I took the only copy.
這些文件太老了  沒備份  我拿走了唯一一份
Okay, send it over. And wash your hands of it.
好吧  發過來  剩下的不用管了
- And add a zero to your bill. - Thanks.
-支票多加一個零  -謝了
Vetril Dease first appears in a 1930 Los Angeles census,
維特利爾·迪斯最早出現于1930年洛城人口普查
living in a low-income home
跟他的父親  母親
with his father, mother and younger sister.
和妹妹住在一處低收入住房
Nine years later, Vetril is listed with his father
九年后  維特利爾和父親成為了僅有的幸存者
as the only survivors of a suspicious fire which swept their house.
他們的房子被一場詭異的火災吞噬
Shortly after the fire, Vetril's named in a court document.
大火之后不久  維特利爾出現在法庭文件中
Citing cruelty beyond the bounds of humanity,
據記載  毫無人性的是
child protection services remove Vetril from his abusive father
兒童保護組織將他從虐待狂父親身邊帶走
and place him in the Good Templars Orphanage in South Vallejo.
送去了位于南瓦萊喬的圣殿騎士孤兒院
His time there is a mystery,
那段時間的經歷是個謎
the only record being his departure at 18.
唯一的記錄就是他18歲時離開了
But the real mystery is what follows.
但真正的謎題是接下來發生的事
Dease disappears for three decades, vanishing like a ghost.
迪斯消失了三十年  人間蒸發
He suddenly resurfaces on the payroll
薩特勒退伍軍人醫院
of the Sawtelle veterans administration,
薩特勒一處老兵機構的工資單上
where he was employed as a janitor for 42 years.
他在那里當門衛長達42年
Dease lived alone and isolated,
迪斯獨居  與世隔絕
using his art to dive deep into his own psyche.
用他的藝術深潛到他的精神世界
The artist battled for decades with his personal demons.
這位藝術家與自己的心魔抗爭了幾十年
The result is an epic saga of violence and madness.
以此換來了這暴力與瘋狂的史詩
A howl for answers and a resolution that never comes.
渴求答案的哀嚎  從未到來的解脫
My ex-boyfriend, Ricky, has an exhibition Friday.
我前男友瑞奇周五有個展覽
He's a hack.
他是個蠢材
A bearded, downtown poser.
滿臉胡須  裝腔作勢
You know, he hasn't had, like, an original idea in his whole life.
他這輩子連一個他自己的主意都沒有
On top of which, he steals from everyone.
除此之外  他剽竊別人的作品
But you know that, right?
但沒關系
I'm very familiar with his work.
我非常熟悉他的作品
You should go to his show,
你應該去看他的展
see for yourself how much he sucks.
親眼看看他有多糟糕
- Then do what you do. - Are you serious?
-然后做你該做的  -你認真的嗎
For me.
為了我
Hello, Morf.
你好  莫弗
Right.
好吧
Is it contemporary?
這是當代的嗎
It cuts through the bullshit and gives form to true emotion.
它直奔主題  賦予了形式真正的情感
- What does it say? - What do you feel?
-這想表達什么  -你感受到了什么
They're using tech in a whole new way.
他們以全新的方式運用科技
The idea is aiming for a platform that includes all media.
主旨在于建立一個包括所有媒介的平臺
He came from nowhere, knew no one,
他不知從何而來  孑然一身
and if our industrious Josephina here hadn't been so observant,
如果不是我們勤勞的約瑟芬娜善于觀察
his genius work would've been thrown away.
他的杰作就可能被丟掉了
And, um, he would've been consigned to oblivion.
他本可能會被遺忘的
I spotted it by a streetlight over a dumpster.
借著路燈  我在一個垃圾堆旁發現的
Approximately, how many pieces are there?
大約一共有多少作品
Well, unfortunately,
很不幸
Mr. Dease's output was the opposite from
迪斯先生可一點
what one would call prolific.
也算不上多產
And he's certainly not making any more.
他也肯定不會有新作品了
There's one we're very interested in.
有一件我們很感興趣
Well, just know demand has people ready to kill.
順便說一聲  大家都搶破頭了
Fetchin'.
真亮眼
Before the sublime, the whole body quivers.
在莊嚴的藝術面前  我忍不住顫抖
Well, at these prices, your museum's locked out.
以這個價格  你們博物館沒戲了
Well, I just yesterday left the museum, so I can speak freely now.
我昨天剛離開了  所以我能隨便說了
- I'm an adviser for a private buyer. - Whom?
-我現在是一位私人買家的顧問  -誰
Our friend who bought Sphere.
買了「球體」的那位
Well, how hilarious for you.
你真幽默呀
In that capacity,
以此為前提
I do have my eye on several of the large-format product for him.
我確實為他挑中幾件大幅畫作
Well, the sales staff have been busy beavers.
銷售人員都忙得團團轉
Everything's on reserve.
所有作品都預定出去了
Perhaps we'd pay a premium.
也許我們可以付定金
- That doesn't butter the biscuit. - Well, what the fuck would?
-這也不能改變什么  -那什么有用
I'll sell you two Dease
我賣給你兩幅迪斯的
if you buy three pieces at Damrish's opening next month.
前提是下個月達米什的首展你買三幅他的畫
What if my client doesn't respond to Damrish?
萬一我的客戶對達米什沒感覺呢
Well, you're the adviser. Advise.
你是顧問  灌輸給他
Damn.
不是吧
Next month, it's your show.
下個月  輪你上場了
I gotta-- I gotta go.
我得走了
Okay.
好的
Isn't it exhilarating to see something substantial?
能看到有實質內容的作品真讓人激動
I mean, other than celebrity tattoo artists and
不只是那些搞刺青的名人藝術家
balloons for painting tools. I'm writing a book about him.
拿氣球當繪畫工具  我在寫關于他的書
I just loathed your Ricky Blane review yesterday.
我很討厭你昨天發表的瑞奇·布萊恩的評論
I thought his show was inspired.
我對他的展覽很受啟發
Well, I didn't get it, I suppose.
可能我沒看懂吧
I felt that we saw totally different exhibits.
我覺得我們看的完全是兩個展
A bad review is better than
負面的評價總好過
sinking into the great glut of anonymity.
消失在平庸之作中  不見天日
- Was that a joke? - Not that I'm aware of.
-那是玩笑嗎  -據我所知不是
Ricky got drunk and crashed his car last night.
瑞奇昨天喝醉了  出了車禍
He's in coma.
他昏迷了
I heard he was crushed.
我聽說他都毀了
By the car?
因為車禍嗎
Your review. Arschloch.
你的評論  王八蛋
What do you mean, Bryson's moving some of the art to storage?
你說什么  布萊森把部分畫作搬去了倉庫
Well, if De Beers released all their diamonds,
如果鉆石商一次發售所有鉆石
they'd be cheap as cut glass.
那它們就會變得一文不值
Didn't they teach any of this in art school?
藝術學校沒教過你這些嗎
How many are we saying he made?
我們要說他有多少作品
Well, their value's their scarcity, so it's not what we say.
它們的價值恰恰在于稀少  所以那不是我們的說辭
It's the reality.
那是事實
The reality is we have over one thousand pieces stored upstairs.
事實是樓上存了一千多幅
Well, that's nonsense.
胡說
Why, I doubt if it's even half that number.
我懷疑都不到五百
What have you done?
你做了什么
Removed them from circulation.
讓它不參與流通
Locking them away for a rainy day.
未雨綢繆
Fuck.
操
Fuck! Fuck!
操  操
shit. shit
該死  該死
Oh shit.
該死
Hello?
有人嗎
Howzit? It's Dondon.
你好啊  我是敦頓
- - Easy, boy. Not yet.
別激動  孩子  沒到時候
Studio visit. I'm excited.
拜訪工作室  我好激動
I can't stomach cheery or upbeat.
我受不了樂天派
I'm not an idiot. Remember that.
我不是傻子  記住了
Hey, I'm honored to be your new representative
我很榮幸成為你的新經紀人
- and see what you've been up to. - I just bet you are.
-看看你最近在忙什么  -我想也是
So, this is where the magic happens?
奇跡發生的地方就是這里嗎
Is that a joke?
這是個笑話嗎
Sorry?
什么
This is repros and replicas.
這些是復制品
Studio's upstairs.
工作室在樓上
Rupert, up.
魯珀特  上樓
This is remarkable.
太壯觀了
It's not art.
那不是作品
Well?
怎么樣
Well, I...
我...
I'm just soaking it in. It's thrilling to see a work in progress.
我還在笑話  親眼看見藝術的產生過程太激動了
Just give me an honest goddamn opinion about
痛快點給我個看法  你眼前的畫
what you're looking at.
到底怎么樣
I can see a line with your body of work. So...
我能看出你作品的特征  所以...
So, I'm copying myself?
我在抄襲自己
It's not copying if it's your canon.
如果是自己的作品  就不算抄襲
I thought your studio was downtown.
我以為你的工作室在城里
Too many addiction triggers.
太多誘惑了
- I worked here the last year. - Well, I--
-我去年都在這工作  -我...
I'd love to see all the new work you've done since moving,
我很愿意看看你搬來之后的所有新作品
because the team is geared up and ready
因為經紀團隊都已經準備好
to sell every new piece you have.
賣出你的所有新作了
Right.
好吧
Sure, of course.
當然了
No, you've... you've been gestating.
不  你在構思
Gestation implies birth.
構思預示著新生
Ideas come, but they kill themselves as soon as they appear.
靈感迸發  然而隨即自我毀滅
This is a slaughterhouse.
這就是個屠宰場
Welcome aboard.
歡迎入伙
When we got the call, it took us a few days to locate you.
我們接到電話后  花了幾天時間找到你們
We've been busy.
我們一直很忙
Now, it looks he slid into the side of a gas station
看起來他滑進了加油站的側面
out in Angeles National Forest.
在加州國家森林公園外
Place has been closed for years.
這里已經關閉幾年了
What caused the crash?
什么導致了車禍
Don't know.
不知道
Think he may have hit his head and wandered off.
也許他撞到頭  就走偏了
It's easy to get lost out there.
這里很容易迷路
Was anything recovered?
有什么發現嗎
Well, we put it in the back here.
都放在后面了
We think the vehicle may have been vandalized before we located it.
我們認為車子在被發現前可能遭到破壞
There's a big homeless camp near there.
這附近有個很大的流浪漢聚集地
They would've cleaned it out if they found it first.
他們如果先找到車子  很可能已經洗劫了
Was there anything of value you know was inside?
你知道車里有什么貴重物品嗎
No.
不
Not that I know of.
據我所知沒有
This is all you found?
你們就找到這些
No.
不
There was this.
還有這個
Where did he go?
他去了哪
Where's the art?
作品都去哪了
Why would you trust him in the first place?
你為什么一開始要相信他
I didn't tell him what was in the crates.
我沒告訴他箱子里是什么
All he had to do was deliver them to a warehouse in Lancaster.
他只需要把箱子運到蘭卡斯特的一個庫房
This shit goes sideways, and I'm telling you straight up,
這事情要出岔子了  跟你明說
I will say this was all your idea. I had nothing to do with it.
我會說這都是你的注意  跟我沒關系
This is Bryson's phone. obviously, I didn't pick up.
這是布萊森的手機  顯然我沒接電話
Bryson, it's me.
布萊森  是我
Where the fuck are you?
你他媽在哪
You trying to strong-arm me, cash in on your own? What?
你要跟我來硬的  自己卷錢跑嗎
Don't fuck with me, Bryson. Call me.
別他媽搞我  布萊森  回我電話
I came at the right time.
我來的時機正好
- - No, no. Not now.
不不  現在不是時候
I have a lot to do.
我有很多事做
Wha... It's not for three hours.
又不是要搞三個小時
It'll take me that long to get ready.
我準備就要花這么久
It's just a fundraiser.
就是個募捐活動
There's going to be pictures.
要拍照的
Our first time out. This is super important to me.
我們第一次一起出席  這對我很重要
I wanna look good.
我想看上去光鮮動人
I found a sick dress.
我找到條不錯的裙子
This sofa's completely too small for the ceiling height.
這個沙發對于天花板的高度來說太小了
It swims in here.
看上去孤零零的
So, I've been cataloging paintings for the book.
我在給那本書歸檔畫作
Something doesn't add up.
但有些不對勁
What's that?
怎么了
There's almost no studies or sketches. They seem to be missing.
里面幾乎沒有研究圖和草圖  看上去遺失了
As well as large gaps from different periods of his work.
不同時期之間也有巨大的空隙
He dated them, you know.
他給畫作標了日期
No, everything I found is there.
不  我找到的都在那了
Trust me, I'd know.
相信我  如果還有我一定會知道的
I've got some great champagne in the fridge.
冰箱里有高檔香檳酒
Open it while we get ready.
我們一邊準備一邊喝吧
Stop by before you leave.
走的時候記得來看看
Your three o'clock is here. Interview for the archivist opening.
三點鐘方向  招聘檔案管理員的面試
You're too young.
你年紀太小了
I'm twenty-two.
我22歲了
The position requires someone with years of experience.
這個職位需要多年的工作經驗
Stop back when you're forty, eh?
等你40歲了再來吧
That's it?
這就完了
That is it.
沒錯
You worked for Rhodora?
你在洛多拉那里干過
Just for a few weeks.
就幾周時間
So, the non-compete clause doesn't apply.
所以我不受非競爭條款的限制
- She fired you? - I was on a break.
-她把你開除了  -我當時在茶歇
A man walked in and talked to her,
有個男的闖進來和她說了幾句話
and she never let it go.
她就揪著這事不放了
You were there for the Dease opening?
你也參加了迪斯的開幕畫展嗎
- It was a zoo. - You know how much she generated?
-亂成了一鍋粥  -你知道她賺了多少嗎
- I saw the numbers. - The buyers list?
-我看到了那筆數目  -買家名單呢
Every name.
每個都知道
Your client bought two.
你的客戶買了兩幅
Very resourceful.
挺機智
I've learned that you have to be.
干這行就必須機智
Rhodora had, um, a file on Dease that she kept locked away.
洛多拉鎖住了一份迪斯的檔案
One day I found the key and...
有天我找到了鑰匙...
it was a very interesting read.
內容非常吸引人
You know what? I might have an opening.
我好像確實有個職位空缺
Come back to my office and tell me what else you heard.
進辦公室跟我說說你還聽到了些什么
I do miss it here.
我還真想念這里呢
The camaraderie, the purity of purpose,
同事情誼  目的純粹
the Tuesday meatloaf,
周二的烘肉卷
the cafe overlooking the tar pits.
還有可以俯瞰瀝青坑的咖啡廳
Well, on to Vetril Dease.
說回正事  維特利爾·迪斯
In the united federation of the universe,
在宇宙聯邦里
I doubt there is a hotter artist at the moment.
現在應該沒有比他更火的畫家了
Do you know, since the exhibit opening,
你知道嗎  自畫展開幕以來
he's actually trending on twitter.
他都上了推特熱門
We're interested in showing him.
我們對展出他的畫作很感興趣
How many pieces are we talking about?
你能提供多少幅
I can supply two owned by my client.
我能提供我客戶買的兩幅
And another ten on loan from the Haze Gallery.
另外還能從迷霧畫廊租借十幅
Send dimensions and JPEGs for the group,
把尺寸和圖片發到群里來
and we'll aim for a spot next season.
我們下個季度開展
I want them exhibited ASAP.
我想馬上就展出
Main hall, new wing. Event marketing.
在主展廳里建個新側廳  還要做活動推廣
You know we have a process, Gretchen.
這都是要走流程的  格雷琴
I had a glorious concept to support my former employer,
我給前雇主想了個絕妙的點子
and supposed premier contemporary art museum of Los Angeles,
給所謂的頂尖洛杉磯當代藝術博物館
with a first showing of a Dease!
率先展覽迪斯的機會
We appreciate the significance,
我們很謝謝你的好意
but there is the issue of space.
但是確實位置不夠
Well, move Banyo's Horse Penis
那就把班尼歐的「馬陰莖」
or the Jeweled Vagina.
或者「鑲寶石陰道」撤掉
Put one inside the other for all I care.
把這兩個合體我也管不著
There is a tax issue,
我的客戶遇到了稅務問題
and my client wants his Dease exhibited immediately.
他想立刻展出他收藏的迪斯畫作
Now, in return for my very generous offer,
為了回報我這個慷慨提議
I also want Minkins' Sphere to be shown.
明金斯的「球體」也要一同展出
Oh, come on, Gretchen, this isn't a rug bazaar.
拜托  格雷琴  我們這里不是地毯集市
No, it's an equation with a solution at the end.
這是個能得到答案的方程式
And if you can't grasp that,
你們要是還不明白的話
there are other museums, I assure you, that will.
我可以肯定  會有其他博物館爭著要的
Kisses.
親親
Sorry.
抱歉
I didn't see you there.
我沒看到你
I'm Morf Vandewalt.
我叫莫弗·范德瓦爾特
I'm here researching Vetril Dease.
我是來調查研究維特利爾·迪斯的
- I'm... writing a book about him. - What for?
-我在寫一本關于他的書  -做什么
He's... He's become a prominent artist
他現在是炙手可熱的畫家
in... in the outsider school.
但是非主流派別
Did... Did you work with him?
你和他共事過嗎
Eighteen years.
18年
Well, it would be extremely helpful
您能不能當幫我個大忙
if we could arrange a time to talk in depth.
我們約個時間深入聊聊他
You see, I have so many questions,
我有很多問題想問
and there's so few people who knew him.
但是知道他的人少之又少
There was a vet you could've talked to.
你本可以去找那個退伍老兵聊的
He had a few medals and a loud mouth.
他有幾枚勛章  還是個大嘴巴
Liked to ride people, particularly Dease.
很喜歡嘲諷人  尤其是迪斯
He wound up dead in a field.
但他最后死在了田里
Hands tied.
雙手被綁著
Never found who did it.
到現在都沒查出兇手
So, you're saying it was Dease?
你的意思是這是迪斯干的
- Damn it! - Oh! Jesus.
-我操  -天哪
I'm saying you left him the fuck alone.
我是要你別再管他的事了
Look, I have nothing more to say.
我沒什么好說的了
And you can tell that other damn fella that, too.
你去跟另外那個家伙也說一聲
Who?
誰
The one who came by here yesterday.
昨天來的那個
I don't know who that would be.
我不知道是誰
Here.
給
Well, we've corroborated Dease's twenty-year incarceration,
我們已經證實迪斯曾被監禁20年
using court documents, police records,
調查內容包括庭審文件  警方記錄
and work history.
還有他的工作經歷
Dease left the Good Templars Orphanage at 18.
迪斯在18歲那年離開了圣殿騎士孤兒院
He was drafted. Served two years in the army.
應征參軍了兩年
And when he got out,
服完兵役后
he suffered some sort of a breakdown.
他遭遇了精神崩潰
At that point,
在那個時候
he tracked down his abusive father and murdered him.
他找到了虐待他的父親并將其殺害
He didn't kill him right away, tho.
但他不是就地殺害的
He dragged it out for days,
而是拖了好幾天
torturing him, then burning him alive.
折磨他  最后把他活活燒死
Dease spent two decades in a psychiatric hospital
迪斯在關押精神病罪犯的醫院里
for the criminally insane.
過了二十年
The facility used inmates for medical experiments.
醫院會用罪犯做醫學實驗
Injections, shocks.
注射  電擊
God knows what else.
天知道還有什么行徑
They were human guinea pigs.
他們就是活體實驗品
Dease got released when the courts closed it.
迪斯在法院關閉醫院之后被釋放了
From there he goes to LA
從那時起他就來到了洛杉磯
and got a job at the veterans home and lived off the grid.
在老兵之家找了個工作  過著隱居生活
No bank account, car, license.
沒有銀行賬戶  汽車和駕照
Couldn't even find a usable photo.
連個可用的照片都沒有
And you verified all this? You're sure?
你確定這些都經過證實了嗎
It all checked out.
都核查過了
Those are the facts.
我說的都是事實
All right, I'm gonna release this tomorrow.
好吧  我明天就發布這些消息
I'm gonna need you to speak to the press,
到時候你得向新聞媒體發言
attesting to your credentials,
證明你的資質
the authenticity of what's in the file, and...
還有文件內容的真實性
and the atrocious and disturbing nature
以及你的這些發現
of what you found, et cetera, et cetera.
是多么的窮兇極惡  令人不安之類的
I thought this kind of stuff would raise the value of his work.
我以為這些信息會讓他的作品升值
Oh, no, no.
那不是
This is another level.
這是另一回事了
- Have a good night. - Nighty-night.
-晚安  -晚安
You've reached Morf. Leave a message.
我是莫弗  請留言
Howzit, Morf? It's Jon.
你好啊  莫弗  我是喬恩
Give me a call back as soon as you can.
請盡快回電
I have something regarding Dease.
我想跟你聊聊迪斯的事
I think might interest you greatly.
你應該會很感興趣
Hello?
有人嗎
What the hell?
搞什么
Jon?
喬恩
Oh, we are just stuck in here, aren't we?
我們一時半會兒是別想走了
What is with that cheesy organ music?
這俗氣的管風琴音樂是怎么回事
And that casket. What color is that?
還有那副棺材  是什么顏色
Smog orange? Did he buy it on sale?
霧橙色  他打折買的嗎
Not so loud.
小聲點說
Seriously, imagine having to spend an eternity in that.
說真的  想想他要永遠都待在那里面
Jesus. Nothing is ever good enough for you.
天啊  你就沒有看得順眼的東西
Well, it's my job. I'm selective.
這是我的工作  我得講究
What are you even saying?
你這話又是什么意思
Toss out taste and standards?
拋掉我的品味和標準
Whisper the truth?
只能低聲說出真相嗎
What a tragic world that would be.
那樣的世界該有多悲慘
I'm Josephina.
我是約瑟芬娜
I work with Rhodora. I'm a partner at the gallery.
我是洛多拉的同事  畫廊合伙人
- Oh, yeah. Damrish. -O h, of course.
-你好  我叫達米什  -我當然知道
- I am just such a huge fan your work. - Thank you.
-我特別喜歡你的作品  -謝謝
I do the Dease collection.
迪斯的收藏是我負責的
It's otherworldly.
你的審美超凡脫俗
- Thank you. - Your review of Hoboman killed the sale.
-謝謝  -因為你的評論讓"流浪俠"滯銷了
Instead of being seen, it's gathering dust at a storage facility.
它沒有受人觀賞  而是在倉庫里落灰
I am not your mouthpiece.
我又不是你的代言人
God.
天啊
We competed for everything,
我們什么事都會爭
but I absolutely despise being here for this.
但我真的很厭惡因為這種事來這里
I mean, what was he facing, to do something like that?
他是遇到了什么事才會做出這種舉動
He was his usual shallow self the last time we spoke.
我們上次談話  他還是不改膚淺的老樣子
Started drinking again.
我又開始喝酒了
Ooh, happy days.
快樂時光又回來了啊
Um, this here is for family and friends only.
這個位置是留給親友的
Well, Jon started at my gallery, so...
喬恩是在我的畫廊做起的
I mean, where the hell else would I sit?
不然我要坐哪里
Ladies and gentleman, if we may begin.
女士們先生們  我們要開始了
- Did you take a Viagra or something? - I'm almost there.
-你是吃了偉哥嗎  -我快射了
No. I'm going on my back.
等下  換后入
- No. - I can't stay like this.
-別  -我這個姿勢不行
Open your eyes.
睜眼
I'm down here.
我在你下面
Oh, God damn it.
我去
Something's wrong.
有點不對勁
We've got a fucking problem. Literally.
我們遇到了操蛋問題  說真的
I'm seeing things, um...
我看到有東西...
Things moving.
有東西在動
Seriously, I'm really scared.
真的  我被嚇著了
I was turned on by your passion,
之前你的熱情讓我欲火焚身
from listening to your intelligent mind,
你睿智的頭腦也是
and now you've turned into I don't know what.
但你現在卻變成了這副鬼樣子
Your reviews have fallen off,
你的評論也掉價了
and you still have feelings for Ed, admit it.
而且你還是忘不掉艾德  承認吧
I do not have feelings for Ed.
我心里已經沒有艾德了
Gretchen ran into him,
格雷琴碰到了他
and he said that you two were talking and working it out.
他說你們還在商量著要繼續走下去
Well, Ed is a big liar,
那艾德就是個大騙子
and Gretchen is a bitch!
格雷琴是個婊子
I checked your phone. You made six calls.
我看了你手機  你打了六通電話
He was moving out, we were coordinating.
我們是在溝通他搬出去住的事情
What do you mean, my reviews have fallen off?
還有你說我的評論掉價是什么意思
Your eye.
你的眼光
Your edge. Makes sense.
你的角度  倒也說得通
You don't know what you like or even want.
你不知道自己喜歡或者想要什么
I'll tell you what I did like.
那我告訴你我到底喜歡什么
Ricky Blane's show.
瑞奇·布萊恩的展
But you jammed me to crush him!
但你逼我毀了他
Don't lay that on me.
別賴我頭上
Like he was your first bad review. Gimme a break.
這又不是你寫的第一篇差評  得了吧
I'm not saying that I blame you.
我沒說我怪你
I'm saying that I regret it.
我是說我很后悔
I think that I've been staring too long
我可能是花了太長時間
at all this Dease art and all his material.
研究迪斯的畫作和資料
I'm... I'm gonna get my vision checked. This will pass.
我過幾天去檢查視力  會好起來的
Listen to my intelligent mind.
聽聽我睿智的想法
Well?
怎么樣
I'm not pickled.
無感
It's a small step, I suppose, toward something, but
可能你這只是剛開頭  但是...
let's talk turkey.
我就實話實說了
What are you afraid of?
你到底在畏懼什么
We go way, way back.
我們是老相識了
I wanna share with you a little somethin' somethin'.
我給你看樣東西
"Dependency murders creativity.
"依賴會扼殺創造力
Creativity plays with the unknown.
創造力和未知作伴
No strategies exist that can enclose the endless realm
沒有任何策略能夠封閉漫無邊際的
of the new.
全新領域
Only trust in yourself
唯有相信自己
can carry you past your fears
才能讓你拋下恐懼
and the already known."
和已知的世界"
That's Polly Anna, 1983.
這是波利·安娜在1983年寫的
I found it clearing out her apartment after she OD'd.
我在她過量用藥后幫她清理公寓時找到的
I gave up being an artist a long time ago,
雖然我很早之前就放棄走畫家這條路了
but I know how this works.
但我知道這一行的規則
Forget about the art world.
先把藝術世界放到一邊吧
You need to get away from here, from all this. Take a break.
你需要逃離這里  這一切  喘口氣
Use my beach house and stay there
你可以住去我的海濱別墅
until you do something for nobody but yourself.
等到你只為自己而活時再回來
Which one's better? One.
哪個更清晰  一號
- Two. - Two.
-還是二號  -二號
All right. Two. One. Better, worse, no different?
好  現在呢  一號二號哪個清晰
No different.
沒區別
All right. There we go.
好了
All right. Well,
好的
your acuity has actually improved since your last prescription.
自上次之后你的視力其實有所提升
I was hoping you'd find something to explain what's happening.
我希望你能找出問題的原因
The phantom movements?
那些幻影移動嗎
I think I have Charles Bonnet syndrome.
我覺得我得了邦納癥候群
Hallucinations, visions, moving objects.
幻覺  幻象  移動的物體
You've been on the Internet. Yeah.
你去谷歌了  我就知道
It's highly doubtful in the absence of other factors.
我覺得不太可能  因為你沒有其他癥狀
But let's make another appointment for this week.
但這周我們再安排一次會診
I dilated your eyes, so you have to wear these for a few hours.
我放大了你的瞳孔  所以你得佩戴幾小時這個
These are heinous.
這實在是丑爆了
Shit.
該死
Fuck.
操
Yes, who is this?
喂  哪位
- It's me. - Oh, how clever. You blocked your number.
-是我  -真聰明  你隱藏了自己的號碼
'Cause you won't answer my calls.
因為你不接我電話
Well, after your vile voice message yesterday, are you surprised?
鑒于你昨天的那通惡毒留言  你很意外嗎
Wha-- I--
什么  我
Telling Josephina I am still with Ed?
你竟然告訴約瑟芬娜我還和艾德在一起
- Oh! That's my crime? - We broke up.
-所以這是我的錯嗎  -我們分手了
I was coordinating with him moving out.
我只是和他商量搬出去的事
Honestly, I expected an apology.
說實話  我期待你會向我道歉
Ed said precisely there was more to it than that.
艾德很明確地說了不止搬家的事
I merely passed it on.
我只是個傳話人
You're a joke!
你真是個天大的笑話
You have no credibility in any way!
沒有任何信譽可言
Oh, really? Well, in that case,
是嗎  既然如此
I suppose there's no truth whatsoever
那我猜你的小伙伴約瑟芬娜
in your little friend Josephina sniffing around Damrish,
圍著達米什轉悠也不是真的了
who, might I add,
容我多嘴一句
are literally about to drive off into the sunset together.
他倆正準備比翼雙飛駛入夕陽呢
Gita?
姬塔
Yes.
我就是
- I'm Morf Vande-- - Vandewalt.
-我是莫弗·范德...  -范德瓦爾特
- Yes. - Of course. I've read you for years.
-沒錯  -當然了  我一直看你寫的藝評
Yes.
幸會
Are those the new Persols?
新買的墨鏡嗎
Yeah. That's right.
嗯  沒錯
That's a Freud.
那是弗洛伊德的畫作
- Yes, it is. - I've never seen that one before.
-沒錯  -我從沒見過這幅
It's been in a crate since '92.
從92年起這幅畫就待在箱子中
And it's going back in one.
同時這也是它的歸宿
I loved your exhibit brochure on Dease, by the way.
對了  我喜歡你制作的迪斯展覽手冊
Thank you.
謝謝
As I said on the phone, I'm expanding it into a book.
正如我在電話里所說  我想把手冊擴寫為一本書
Well, there's enough there for one.
內容肯定綽綽有余
You cataloged the collection presale.
你編目了售前展覽的作品
Oh, not cataloged.
沒有編目
My primary focus became Dease's distinctive methodology.
我的工作重心變成了研究迪斯獨特的作畫方法
I spent three weeks identifying conventions,
我花了三周時間研究習俗
workflow, classifications.
工作流程  作品分類
It was almost impossible to delineate
幾乎無法區分
between working materials and personal effects.
作畫材料和個人物品
Frankly, I was glad to finish.
說實話  我很高興完成了
Well, I wasn't aware there were any personal effects
我不知道除了我手里的那些作品
besides the ones in my possession.
還有其他的個人物品
None in a traditional sense.
不是傳統意義上的個人物品
I mean, as in tissue.
我是說組織[紙巾]一類的
Paper?
畫紙嗎
Perhaps you should speak with Rhodora.
也許你該和洛多拉談談
Rhodora is...
洛多拉
backing the book.
非常支持這本書
I have her full support and confidence, of course.
不用多說她全力支持我且對我有信心
Tissue as in blood serum.
血清那種組織
The artist's, I assume.
我猜是畫家自己的血清
He used it to create the reddish blacks and the shadows.
他用血清調出了黑紅色和陰影
It was in every piece we studied.
我們研究的每幅畫里都有
That is an outrageous request. Even coming from you.
即使是你  這個要求也太過分了
I don't get your pushback on a Minkins retrospective here,
我不懂你們為什么要推遲展出明克斯的作品
in the fall, of all his major works.
不過是在秋季展出他所有的主要作品
We already agreed to put up Sphere
我們已經同意展出「球體」
in exchange for you bringing us twelve Dease.
來換你的十二幅迪斯畫作
Seriously, Gretchen, it's rude and dumb.
說真的  格雷琴  這么做既無禮又愚蠢
If you wanted to ram more of your collector's hoard
如果你想把你老板手中的藏品
down our throats to increase their value,
強塞給我們以增加其價值
you should have done so before the Dease deal was locked,
你應該在決定展出迪斯之前就下手
not the night before the exhibit's open.
而不是在展覽的前一天晚上
I hear marketing has high hopes of a traveling Dease collection.
我聽說市場部很期望做迪斯作品巡回展
They've even run projections.
他們甚至已經做了個規劃
So, I believe my "Leverage" looking ahead is considerable.
所以我相信我的籌碼還是很可觀的
There's absolutely no space in the fall to put on a Minkins show.
秋季絕對沒有檔期展出明克斯的作品了
Well, I'm going to meet with your board tomorrow
明天我要和你們的董事會見面
and suggest a reduction in the emerging artist exhibit.
建議減少新興藝術家展覽
They don't sell any tickets anyway.
反正它們也不賣座
Over my dead body.
想得美
Gretchen?
格雷琴
The hard copy PR material's been sorted,
官宣材料稿件已經整理好
and the electronic kits get sent at midnight.
電子工具盒半夜已發出
Be here early.
明天早點來
And inform me of any celebrities or art stars.
并提前告訴我到場的任何明星或藝術家
Um, if it's all right with you,
如果可以的話
I'd like to go home and get a few hours of sleep?
我想回家休息幾小時
Has the lighting been corrected on Sphere?
「球體」的燈光調整了嗎
Oh, the side lights, yes. I had them leave it lit,
側燈  是的  我留了側燈
so you could see it when you leave.
這樣你離開時就能看見它了
Then run along.
那你回去吧
Good night.
晚安
Help!
救命
Hello.
喂
No.
不會吧
When?
什么時候
This morning.
今天早上
Somehow she got stuck inside of it.
不知怎么地她被卡在了里面
There was some kind of malfunction, and I guess it just, like,
發生了一些故障  然后我猜大概是
completely took her arm off and she bled to death.
作品把她整個手臂卸了  她因失血過多死亡
It was horrible.
太可怕了
Security guards thought it was part of a new installation,
保安以為尸體是藝術品的新裝置
so they just opened up and let people in.
所以他們開門讓人們進去參觀了
The Dease pop-up announcement was blasted last night,
昨晚迪斯展覽的彈出窗口宣傳大獲成功
so everyone was heading there.
所以大家都前去參觀
People just walked by like she was part of an exhibit.
人們走過她的尸體  仿佛她是展覽的一部分
Then a school tour came along.
然后來了一群學校的孩子
The kids thought it was fake blood,
孩子們以為地上是假血
so they just started stepping in it
于是就開始踩著玩
and spreading it around and...
并踩得到處都是
Who knows how long it would have gone on for
如果不是可可要處理迪斯展覽的新聞發布
until Coco came in to do press for the Dease show,
誰知道這群小孩會玩到什么時候
and she saw Gretchen and just lost it.
可可看到了格雷琴后直接就奔潰了
Are you still there?
你還在嗎
Rhodora?
洛多拉
I don't understand.
我不明白
Bryson, then Jon. Now Gretchen.
先是布萊森  然后喬恩  現在又是格雷琴
What the fuck is going on?
到底怎么回事
I don't know.
我不知道
I mean, we just saw her last night.
我們昨晚才見過她
They closed that wing of the museum, but...
他們關閉了博物館的那棟樓  但是
I hear the Dease exhibit is mobbed.
我聽說迪斯的展覽人滿為患
Hey. Go.
走開
We're spiking on Moments and Instagram. It's a major hit.
我們在朋友圈和照片墻火爆了  上了熱搜榜
Rhodora, are you still there?
洛多拉  你還在嗎
Did you hear what I just said?
你聽見我剛說的了嗎
Yeah.
聽見了
The Dease exhibit is booming.
迪斯的展覽風生水起
There's someone at my door. I gotta go.
有人敲門  我得掛了
Did you...
你有沒有...
hear about Gretchen?
聽說格雷琴的事
Did you?
你聽說了嗎
Oh, Jesus.
我的天
- Can you believe it? - You have to leave.
-你能相信嗎  -你得走了
You just can't, well, just walk in like this!
你不能就這樣  這樣進來
Well, I need to be with someone right now.
我現在不想一個人待著
I'd think you would, too.
我覺得你也是
What's going on?
怎么回事
Are you kidding me?
你在逗我玩嗎
We're not together. I was clear.
我們沒在約會  之前我就說明白了
You said, "A break."
你說"暫時分開"
The admiration I had for your work
我對你作品的景仰之情
has completely evaporated!
已經完全消失殆盡
Hey, man, I wasn't trying to jump your train, okay?
老兄  我可沒打算奪你所愛  好嗎
She said you two were done.
她說你倆玩完了
Are we? Are we?
是嗎  是嗎
Say we don't share something real.
說我們倆之前沒有真情實感
I was never particularly obsessed.
我從沒有特別著迷你
We expected you yesterday.
我們昨天就盼著您來了
We closed the exhibit for half a day in anticipation, actually.
我們閉展半日  期待著您的大駕光臨
I thought Artweb were clear on the timing.
我以為藝術網站把時間說的很清楚
I know, I'm sorry. It's my fault.
我知道  抱歉  是我的錯
I know it's pre-debut.
我知道這是首展
Just been experiencing some personal matters.
只是我最近有些私事要處理
Then, of course, Gretchen this morning.
然后  你懂的  今早格雷琴的慘劇
- If this isn't a good time... - No, it's fine.
-如果現在不是時候...  -不  沒關系
It's overdue.
我早該來了
I'll write my review and file it today.
我今天就把評論寫好并發出
Lillith Vanlandingham is storming the world
莉莉斯·范蘭迪根用她的革新性
with her revolutionary sound exhibits.
聲音展覽沖擊著世界的耳膜
She won the Nam June Paik Award last year.
去年她獲得了白南準藝術中心獎
Her latest piece is called Mysticete.
她最新的作品叫做「須鯨」
As discussed,
根據約定
we have arranged for you to experience the exhibit alone.
我們安排讓您單獨體驗展覽
Look at him standing there.
瞧瞧他站在那
He only embraces what he knows.
他只接受自己懂得的藝術
Undoubtedly one of the worst exhibits of contemporary art history.
毫無疑問是現代藝術歷史上最糟糕的展覽之一
Piece for piece,
一塊又一塊
it's the biggest waste of steel since the Titanic.
這是自泰坦尼克號以來浪費鋼鐵最嚴重的一次了
This painful exhibit should be bulldozed.
這種令人痛苦的展覽就該被連根鏟除
Remove the spotlight of hype and his latest work is a snoozefest.
去掉天花亂墜的炒作  他新作就是場無聊盛宴
Seriously, Ms. Minati, I am talking to you.
不是開玩笑  米納蒂女士  我在和你說話
It seems you have no one around you to say this. Stop it.
似乎你周圍沒有人告訴你  停下吧
Shut up the shed.
放棄吧
There are no redeeming qualities to the show.
這場展覽毫無可取之處
Nothing but embarrassed-- The best thing about the show
只有難堪  展覽唯一的亮點
is the French rosé being offered.
就是供應了法國桃紅葡萄酒
It's an ugly piece to look at, and faintly nauseating.
這幅作品丑陋得無法直視  還會引起輕微反胃
It's gone from innocent and stupid...
從無知愚蠢升級到...
I'll hate you forever for saying that!
你這句話我會記恨一輩子
- Lazily concealed. - Vile. Deceitful!
-毫不上心地隱藏  -卑鄙  騙子
Deceitful!
騙子
Morf!
莫弗
Judgment should be judged.
評論也該被評價
It is a monumental failure.
這是一場巨大的失敗
Morf!
莫弗
Ricky Blane is the classic case
瑞奇·布萊恩是典型的
of presenting a poser as cutting edge.
裝腔作勢引領潮流的冒牌貨
Sorry for the delay. Our computer crashed.
抱歉耽擱了  剛才電腦死機了
We're-- We'll start it now.
我們  我們現在就開始
What did I just hear?
那我剛才聽到的是什么
Nothing. This is a soundproof room.
什么也沒放  這是一間隔音房
Voi...
聲...
Voices.
各種聲音
I've no idea.
我不知道
Mysticete is a symphony of whale intonation
「須鯨」是一場馬里亞納海溝下
recorded 20,000 feet under the sea in the Mariana Trench.
兩萬英尺處鯨魚抑揚頓挫聲調相互交融的交響樂
You are up for this?
您準備好了嗎
I am seeing things.
我看見了一些東西
I'm hearing things.
聽到了不存在的聲音
Unexplainable things.
無法解釋的事情
Impossible things.
不可能發生的事情
And this is hard to admit
作為現世主義的擁護者
as an adherent of the here and now
和堅定鄙夷幼稚迷信的我來說
and a denier of childish belief.
承認這一點很困難
But something truly goddamn strange is going on!
但有離奇至極的事情正在發生
What happened to Bryson?
布萊森到底怎么了
According to the police, he had an accident
根據警方調查  他出了車禍
and he wandered into the desert.
然后神志恍惚走入了沙漠
I spoke to the police.
我和警察談過
They have video surveillance
他們有布萊森
of the night that Bryson went missing.
失蹤當晚的監控錄像
He was loading crates of art into his truck.
他的卡車裝著滿滿幾箱藝術品
Okay.
好吧
What was in those crates?
那些箱子里是什么
And all this relates how?
與這些事又有什么關系
Dease!
迪斯
His altered mental state,
他扭曲的精神狀態
tortured soul, phases of the goddamn moon!
受盡折磨的靈魂  月亮的陰晴圓缺
I don't know how!
我不知道是如何發生的
These deaths.
但這些死亡
The disappearance.
失蹤
Everything that is now happening,
現在正發生的一切
it's all connected to his art.
都跟他的作品有關
Imbued with some spirit...
他的畫里有邪靈
cr... created out of some vital ideal.
或是根據某種致命的原型創作
It's a bit Baroque, don't you think?
這有點巴洛克  你不覺得嗎
- I came here to warn you. - Okay.
-我是來警告你的  -好吧
You know what? It's been a fucked-up few weeks!
我知道這幾周很混亂難熬
But listen to yourself!
但你聽聽自己說的瘋話
I spoke to the building owners during research.
我做調查時找大樓業主聊過
They were surprised
他們聽說
to hear Dease's art was being sold.
迪斯的作品在出售  都很驚訝
Apparently,
顯然
he left explicit instructions that it all be destroyed.
他留下了很明確的遺言  要把作品全銷毀
- What are you saying? - Stop selling Dease!
-你想說什么  -別再賣迪斯的作品了
It's an eight-figure collection...
他的藏品能賣八位數
...and you want me to stop selling over some spirit?
就因為什么幽靈  你想讓我停止出售嗎
I am writing an article about this.
我在寫一篇與這有關的文章
About Dease, his past, his methods,
關于迪斯  他的過去  他的方法論
everything that has gone down.
所發生的所有事
- Well, you'll kill your career. - Get rid of it.
-你會毀了自己的事業  -把作品處理掉
Box it all, all of it away.
都裝進盒子里扔掉
That's what I'm doing.
我就準備這么做
All art is dangerous, Morf.
所有藝術都是危險的  莫弗
Oh, it's just been a feeding frenzy since the debut.
首次展出后就有很多人競相出價
What's changed is we ran new metrics and realized that
但經過重新衡量  我們發現
we've been overly precious with supply.
對供貨的數量過于謹慎了
I sent you six Dease JPEGs,
我給你發了六張迪斯作品的圖片
all available for immediate purchase at the quoted price
都可以立即以報價購買
and destined for significant appreciation.
這些作品一定會大幅升值
All of them. Well, that's swell.
全都買下嗎  太好了
I'll send the papers.
我把相關文件發給你
Okay. Yeah.
好的
I'll see you in Basel.
我們在巴塞爾見
What's going on?
怎么回事
We closed the first phase on Dease. Why are we selling more?
迪斯的首期銷售不是結束了嗎  為什么繼續出售
Morf is hell-bent on writing a story.
莫弗執意要寫一篇文章
He's connecting Bryson's disappearance
他覺得布萊森的失蹤
and Jon and Gretchen's deaths to the Dease art.
喬恩和格雷琴的死  都與迪斯的作品有關
He believes they're somehow channeling some sort of...
他認為那些作品以某種方式引出了某種...
spirit.
邪靈
What kind of spirit?
什么邪靈
I don't know the varieties.
我對這種事又不了解
So he writes some batshit story. Who cares?
就算他寫瘋狂的故事又怎樣  沒人在乎
We don't sell durable goods, we peddle perception.
我們不是在賣耐用品  而是傳播概念
Thin as a bubble.
一戳即破
Call your buyers,?
打給你的買家們
sell as much Dease as you can before he posts something.
在莫弗發表文章前  盡量多賣出幾幅迪斯
- Who's next? - You have Roxy on one.
-下一個是誰  -羅克西在一線
Hey, babe.
親愛的
Checking back on you wanting some museum-quality Dease.
你之前說想買幾幅有收藏價值的迪斯
Baby, that's raw silk. Your shoes.
寶貝  沙發是生絲的  腳放下來
Pop this.
把瓶蓋打開
You've got strong hands.
你的手勁真大
You ever look at this painting?
你有沒有認真看過這幅畫
You ever notice anything about this painting?
你有發現過異常嗎
You look at it long enough and it moves.
只要一直盯著看  畫就會動
It's alive.
這幅畫是活的
- I've just sold it. - What? I would have bought it.
-我剛把這幅畫賣了  -什么  我本來也想買
You couldn't afford it.
你又買不起
We don't want it. Trust me, I'm doing you a favor.
我們不想要的  相信我  我這是在幫你
I gotta get down to Traction Avenue.
我得趕去特拉克遜大道
- I thought we were spending the night in. - Yeah.
-我們不是今晚打算在家里度過嗎  -本來是
Something just came up, and I gotta take care of it tonight.
但剛發生了些事  我今晚必須去處理
You're blowing me off.
你要放我鴿子
I want you to come.
我想要你一起來
Why do you keep calling me?
你為什么一直打給我
Why?
你還問為什么
We break up,
我們分手
and you write an article to completely destroy my livelihood.
你就寫一篇文章來徹底毀掉我的生計
I am not doing this to get back at you.
我這么做不是為了報復你
It's Dease's art.
是因為迪斯的作品
I think any of us who profited from it are in danger.
通過他作品獲利的人都有危險
So, you just blasted it out there?
所以你就昭告天下嗎
Jesus Christ. I am reading it right now.
老天  我現在正在讀你的文章
Are you aware that you've completely lost your mind?
你知不知道自己徹底瘋了
We don't realize the value of friends until they're gone.
直到失去后  我們才意識到朋友有多重要
I still consider you a friend, Josephina.
我仍視你為朋友  約瑟芬娜
Go fuck yourself and lose my number!
你去死吧  把我號碼刪了
Well, fine, then. Bye.
那好吧  再見
Hello?
喂
It's Morf.
我是莫弗
A timetable is moved up.
我計劃有變
I'm storing some art and I'm leaving immediately.
我要存放一些畫作  但我馬上要離開
I need an assistant part-time here while I'm gone.
我不在的期間  需要一個兼職助手幫我
- Well, I'm available. - Yeah. Can you start tonight?
-我有空  -今晚就開工可以嗎
I guess so. Sure.
應該可以  沒問題
I need to give you the keys to my house and my storage space.
我要把我家和儲存室的鑰匙給你
There's an overlook on Mulholland, right off Cahuenga.
穆赫蘭大道上有個觀景臺  剛過卡漢加路口
- I know the one. - Good. I'll meet you there.
-我知道在哪里  -很好  我在那里等你
Mr. Vandewalt. Hi.
范德瓦爾特先生  你好
I posted it, Coco.
那篇文章我發了  可可
And with this article,?I'm... I'm...
文章發出去之后  我...
I'm pouring gas on myself. I'm lighting a match.
我等于往自己身上澆汽油  點燃火柴
I don't have a choice.
但我別無選擇
It has been revealed to me
我現在知道了
that there is some sort of larger power...
有某種更強大的力量
some entity invested in our endeavor.
某種物質  存在于我們的事業
Invested how?
怎么存在
In...
通過
the violation
違反
of inviolate rules.
不可違反的規則
Have I gone mad?
我是不是瘋了
Not to me.
我不認為
I found both bodies.
我可是發現了兩具尸體
I'm sleeping with my lights on.
我睡覺都不敢關燈
On top of which, if I don't land a steady job soon,
除此以外  如果我再不找到穩定工作
I'm gonna have to go back to Michigan.
我就得回密歇根老家了
I have to tell you something.
有件事我必須告訴你
What?
什么事
I was Rhodora's personal assistant, right?
我之前不是擔任過洛多拉的私人助理嗎
I saw her checks, I rolled calls with her.
我看過她的支票  我幫她轉接電話
I think she sometimes forgot when I was on them.
她有時好像忘記我也在線上
Tell me.
告訴我
Your ex-boyfriend, Ed, um...
你的前男友  艾德
he worked for her.
他之前為她工作
He worked her out. He's a personal trainer.
他幫她健身  他是私教
No.
不
No, I mean...
不  我是指
Rhodora paid Ed to give her advance word on your reviews.
洛多拉雇用艾德  讓他提前把你的評論告訴她
Like, okay... He would tell her what you liked before you posted,
就是  他會在你發表評論前把你喜歡的作品告訴她
and then she'd make buys.
然后她就買下那些作品
Do I still have the job?
我沒被你炒魷魚吧
Here are the keys to my storage space.
這是我的儲存室的鑰匙
I need everything itemized that's there.
你把里面所有作品做好詳細登記
Okay.
好的
Is my car safe out there?
我的車停在外面安全嗎
How the fuck should I know?
我他媽鬼知道
Where did you go?
你去哪了
This is Ben. He runs my old artist collective.
這是本  他代理我以前的系列作品
Lovely. Can we go now?
很好  我們可以走了嗎
I'm staying.
我要留下來
But I don't really like this place.
但我不太喜歡這里
Yeah, I'm talking longer timeline.
我是指更長期的打算
I'm leaving Rhodora, her gallery.
我打算離開洛多拉和她的畫廊
No, you're not.
你不能離開
I can't be there.
我沒法待在那
We have a significant show planned. You're high. Come on.
我們準備辦一場盛大的展覽  你嗑嗨了  走吧
I'm serious.
我是認真的
You're about to break big.
你馬上就要獲得重大突破
We're taking you global.
我們會讓你名揚世界
You'd give that up? For what?
你愿意放棄這些嗎  為了什么
Some sad garage space peddling graffiti murals?
在可悲的車庫里叫賣涂鴉壁畫嗎
Jesus! What's the point of art if nobody sees it?
老天  如果沒人看到  藝術還有什么意義
Fuck!
操
Yeah, there's a car blocking my car. I want it towed.
有輛車擋住了我的車  請過來拖走它
I don't know.
我不知道
Hang on.
稍等
Oh, 2057 Seventh Street.
第七街2057號
I'm waiting.
我在這等著
Hello?
有人嗎
I'm just waiting for a tow truck.
我只是進來等拖車
Oh, thank God.
謝天謝地
Hello?
喂
Damrish is leaving.
達米什要走
He met his old exhibitor in a dive bar
他剛才在廉價酒吧跟他以前的代理人見面
and told me he's going back. It's over.
他說要回去  結束了
Good for him.
對他來說是好事
What do you mean, good for him? What are you talking about?
這話是什么意思  你在說什么
Josephina, are you aware
約瑟芬娜
that Dease asked that all his art be destroyed?
你知道迪斯要求把自己作品全部銷毀嗎
Would it have changed anything?
銷毀了難道就會有什么不同嗎
Would I have destroyed them?
我要是知道了  當初會銷毀嗎
No.
不會
He was a master.
他是藝術大師
Oh, Jesus. Hold on, Josephina.
天吶  稍等  約瑟芬娜
Stella.
斯黛拉
Stella. Stella.
斯黛拉  斯黛拉
Stella. God damn it.
斯黛拉  該死
Have you ever felt invisible?
你感受過被忽視嗎
Once, I built a railroad.
我曾經建過鐵路
Rhodora?
洛多拉
Come on, Stella. Come on. Come on.
過來  斯黛拉  過來
Stella, come.
斯黛拉  過來
Come on, good girl. Good girl.
來  乖貓咪  乖貓咪
Come on, Stella! Damn it!
別跑  斯黛拉  該死
Stella!
斯黛拉
Rhodora?
洛多拉
Oh, my God.
天吶
Oh, my... Oh my...
天吶  天吶
No, no! No! I understand!
不  不  我不懂
I understand!
我不懂
I can't save you.
我救不了你
Jesus Christ, I can't believe what just happened.
老天  真不敢相信剛才發生的事
Josephina? Hello?
洛多拉  通話中
Where...
哪里...
Oh, fuck me!
我操
What?
什么
How?
怎么會
A storage facility?
儲物倉庫
Well, what do they think happened?
他們認為發生了什么
No. I'm not coming in.
不  我不回畫廊了
I gotta go.
我得掛了
Pick up the phone.
快接電話
Yeah, we got it.
找到車了
No sign of the owner.
沒看見車主
We're taking it to Central.
我們準備把車拖回總部
Yeah.
好
That's all of it.
都搬完了
Everything?
所有都搬完了嗎
Every image, every drawing, every postcard,
每張圖  每幅畫  每張明信片
every piece of art?
每件藝術品都搬完了
- Say it. - It's completely empty.
-說出來  -都搬空了
Forty-seven pieces. We removed everything.
一共47件  我們都搬走了
Thank you.
謝謝你
- LAX. Terminal five. - Okay.
-去洛杉磯機場  五號航站樓  -好的
- That's lovely. - Yeah.
-真好看  是啊
How much?
多少錢
I don't know. Five dollars.
五美元好了
Yeah.
好
Thank you.
謝謝你
Here you go.
給
- Thanks. - Take care.
-謝謝  -保重